Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Sanchez, Jennifer, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Sanchez-Buscemi, America, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 38)
- Sandager, Matthew, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- Sandler, Ilan, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 40)
- Sanford, Tom, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 42)
- Sansour, Larissa, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 45)
- Santaniello, Carmine, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 46)
- Santiago, Maria, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Santibanez, Katia, 1988-1997 (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Santos, Nelson, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 47)
- Sapir, Marc, 2001-2005 (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Sapp, Tommy, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Sarafin, Peter, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 50)
- Sarkilahti, Jennifer, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Sarmiento, Jeffrey, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Sartori, M. Luisa, 1992-1999 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Sasowsky, Norman, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Sass, Julie, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Sasson, Gale, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Sato, Hidemi, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Sauerbrun, Susan J., 2002 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sautter, Sebastian, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Savannah, Gae, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Savolainen, Alli, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Sax, Alexandra, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Sayegh, Riva, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Sayegh, Sharon, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Sayler, William, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Saylor, Suzanne, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Scally, Gwyneth, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Scardillo, Sante, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Scarlata, Ann, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Schaad, Robert, 1995-2001 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Schaefer, Barbara, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Schaefer, Barbara Rae, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Schaefer, Robert, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Schaeffer, Beth, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Schaer, Miriam, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Schafer, Lori, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Schall, Michael, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Schaller, Rhonda, 1991-1999 (Box 64, Folder 58)
- Schanen, Deirdre, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Schapira Caplan, Susan, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Schatz, Lincoln, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Schatz, Robert, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 30)
- Scheider, Judy Lyons, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Scheifele, Kristina, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 32)
- Schellenberg, Lou, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 36)
- Schellinger, Bryan, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- Schenker, Irys, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 33)
- Schenning, Matthew, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 38)
- Scher, Daniel, 1994-2001 (Box 48, Folder 39)
- Scherl, Alexis, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 40)
- Schiele, Kristen, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 42)
- Schifano, Karen, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 41)
- Schifano, Karen, 1989-1995 (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Schiffman, Jacquelyn, 1993-1995 (Box 48, Folder 35)
- Schille, Carol, 1992-2000 (Box 48, Folder 43)
- Schille, Carol, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 44)
- Schinz, Maria, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 45)
- Schipper, Jonathan, 1994-1999 (Box 64, Folder 57)
- Schlefer, Dick, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 46)
- Schlefer, Dick, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 47)
- Schleider, Nicky, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 48)
- Schlesinger, Karen, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 49)
- Schluenz, Jon, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 50)
- Schmacke, Claudia, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 51)
- Schmelzer, Thomas, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 56)
- Schmidt, Jennifer, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 52)
- Schmidt, Patrick, 2000-2003 (Box 48, Folder 53)
- Schmidlapp, David, 1980s (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Schnall, Kenneth, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 54)
- Schneider, Tina, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 55)
- Schoener, Silke, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 57)
- Schoenfeld, Ketti Rae, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 60)
- Schooley, Cynthia, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 58)
- Schorr, Justin, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 59)
- Schranz, Jordon, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 60)
- Schreiber, Leah, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 61)
- Schroll, Savannah, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Schurr, Thomas, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 63)
- Showbim, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Schultz, Jennifer, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 61)
- Schulz, Charlotte, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Schwartz, Molly, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 62)
- Schwartz, Peri, 1989-2001 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Schwartz, Steve, 1989-1999 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Schwartz, Susanna, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Schwarz, Gretchen, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Schwede, Matt, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Sciandra, Aaron, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Scott, Ann, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Scott, Lizzie, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Scott, Marigold, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Scott, Sue, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Scruggs, Loran, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Seaberg, Libby, 1994-2000 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Seaberry, Monica, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Seborg, Susie, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Sedgwick, Chris, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Sedgwick, Martha, 1988-2003 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Seeger, Zachary, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Segura, Pilar, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Sehaefer, Carey Ann, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Seid, Dui, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Seiple, Daniel, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Sekeres, Ann Marie, 1998-2001 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Selbo, Vivian, 1989-1993 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Seldom, Harry, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Selekman, Rachel, 1990-2004 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Selleck, Colin, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Sellmann, Bettina, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Seltzer, Phyllis, 1995-2002 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Sendor, Andrew, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Senior, Andrew, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Sepuya, Paul, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Sera, Kyoko, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Seroka, Lenore, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Serra, Shelter, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Serrano, Adriana, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Servidio, Giuseppe, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 40)
- Sexton, Joseph, 1997-1998 (Box 64, Folder 64)
- Sfraga, Denise, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 47)
- Shafer, Kathleen, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Shafir, Lisa, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- Shalala, Edward, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Shalat, Neal, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 44)
- Shales, Ezra, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Shandler, Manju, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Shannon, Cate, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 46)
- Shapira, Galia, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Shapiro, David, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Shapiro, Manya, 1995-2001 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- Sharma, Arun, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 47)
- Sharon, Russel, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 82)
- Sharp, Keith, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Sharp, Susan, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- Sharrett, Donna, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Shechter, Laura, 1994-2001 (Box 49, Folder 55)
- Sheehan, Carolyn, 1995-1999 (Box 49, Folder 56)
- Sheehan Saldana, Zoe, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 57)
- Shein, Meagan, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 58)
- Shein, Meagan, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 59)
- Sheirr, Olga, 1988-1999 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Sheldon, Jay, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Sheldon, Joshua, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Sheng, Michael, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- SHEPHERD, SHAWN, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Sher, Vicki, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Sherin, Kathleen, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Sherin, Robin, 1999-2002 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Sherman, Rebecca, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Sherrill, Milton, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Shields, Lela, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Shields, Maureen, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Shih, Bullet, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Shim, Jeong Eun, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Shim, Jung Rhee, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Shimooka, Takafumi, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Shin, Hyungsub, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Shin, Jean, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Shinkarev, Stephanie, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Shipley, Richard, 1987-1991 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Shirai, Mio, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Shirobayashi, Kiriko, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Shkolnik, Asya, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Shoemaker, Pamela, 1999-2001 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Shorb, Bethany, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Shostrom, Ann, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Shoub, Darrell, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Shoub, Jaclyn, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Shpungin, Diana, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Shterenberg, Marina, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Shterenberg, Marina, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Shuldiner, Gabriel J., 2005 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Siazon, JD, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Siddiqi, Joseph, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 36)
- Siedlecki, Heidi, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 65)
- Siegal, Erin, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- Siegel, Joyce, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 33)
- Siegel, Fran, 1989-1994 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Sierra, Paul, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Sigillo, Lissi, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 37)
- Sigillo, Lissi, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Silberman, Richard, 1995-1998 (Box 50, Folder 39)
- Silva, Bela, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 45)
- Silva, Mario, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 40)
- Silva, Thomas, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 41)
- Silvers, Regina, 2001-2003 (Box 50, Folder 42)
- Silverstein, Sasha, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 43)
- Silvi, Stephanie, 2000-2005 (Box 50, Folder 44)
- Silvia, Pet, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 46)
- Silvio, Dominic, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 47)
- Simeti, Francesco, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 48)
- Simmons, Daniel, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 49)
- Simmons-JImenez, Alette, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 50)
- Simon, Deborah, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 51)
- Simonds, Nancy, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 52)
- Simone Spencer, Anastasia, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 53)
- Simonson, Elizabeth, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 54)
- Simpson, Allan, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 55)
- Sims, Gabrielle, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 56)
- Sinawi, Ayad, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 57)
- Singer, Christian Bernard, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 60)
- Singer, Greg, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 58)
- Singletary, Gregory, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 61)
- Sinocchi, Karenann, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 59)
- Sinsabaugh, Elisabeth, 1995-1998 (Box 50, Folder 62)
- Sissman, Liron, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 63)
- Sittler, Rebecca, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 64)
- Sivilli, Val, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 65)
- Sjuve, Eva, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 66)
- Skerlj, Davide, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Skinner, Conrad, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Skinner, Steven, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Skolnick, Judith, 1996-2001 (Box 64, Folder 66)
- Skopitz, Hyla, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Skou, Lise, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Skrzynski, Jackie, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Skvirsky, Karina, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Skwentna, Greg, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Slatky, Michael, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Slauenwhite, Susanne, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Slaymaker, Jill, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Slemmons, Becky, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Sloan, Jennifer, 1988-2001 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Sloane, Louise, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Smaka, Stashu, 1990-2001 (Box 64, Folder 67)
- Small-Gamby, Julie, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Smilen, Steven, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Smit, Tanja, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Smith, Adam, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Smith, Adam Parker, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Smith, Alix, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Smith, Allison, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 68)
- Smith, Allyson, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Smith, Anthony, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Smith, Casey Jex, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Smith, Colin, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 69)
- Smith, Curtis, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Smith, Cynthia, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Smith, Ian, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Smith, Jud, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Smith, Kimanne, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Smith, Kristy Lynn, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Smith, Mike Peter, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Smith, Mike Peter, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Smith, Monica, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Smith, Nico, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Smith, Rene, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- Smith, Roxa, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Smith, Sarah, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Smith, Shannon, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 35)
- Smith, Thom, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 36)
- Smith, Tremain, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 37)
- Smith, Tremain, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Smith, Tremain, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 39)
- Smits van Burgst, Niels Edo Richard, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 40)
- Smokler, Stan, 1994-2001 (Box 51, Folder 41)
- Smolinski, Susan, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Smolinski, Susan, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Smook, Diane, 1999-2003 (Box 51, Folder 44)
- Smulcheski, Fran, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Snelgrove, Tom, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Sniffen, Frances, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 47)
- Snow, Shawn, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 48)
- Snyder, Todd, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 49)
- Sobieralski, Casondra, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Soderberg, Janet, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 51)
- Sohn, Mi Young, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 52)
- Sohrens, Claudia, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 53)
- Soika, Karin Ulrike, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 54)
- Sokolin, Deanne, 1992-2001 (Box 51, Folder 55)
- Sokolov, Joel, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 56)
- Sokolowska, Ursula, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 57)
- Sol-Dyess, Judith, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Solbert, R.G., 1995 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Solin/Iacone, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Solmi, Federico, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Solomon, Carrie, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Solomon, Elke, 1988-1990 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Solomon, Marsha, 1989-2005 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Solon, H. Lisa, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Soltis, Melissa, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Son, Han Sam, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Song, Jong Rim, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Song, Miyoung, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Songco, Jeffrey Augustine, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Sonntag, Stefan, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Sono, Keiko, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Soreff, Stephen, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Sorrentino, Pasquale, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Soskolne, Lise, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Soto, Lisa, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Sourget, Amelie, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Sovinc, Peter, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Spalding, Kelly, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Spalding, Kelly, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- Spangler, Ted, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- Spann, Susan, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Sparatley, Gigi, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Sparkman, Barry, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Spath, Christoph, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- Spaulding, Brent, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 29)
- Spears and Nayadley, 1999-2002 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- Speiss, Anne-Katrin, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 31)
- Spector, Maria, 1994-2003 (Box 52, Folder 32)
- Spektor, Yury, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- Spell, Sharon Mama, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Spence, Taylor, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 35)
- Sperber, Devorah, 1994-2002 (Box 52, Folder 36)
- Speshilov, Alina, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 106)
- Spevack, Jenna, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 37)
- Spielman, Anya, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 38)
- Spiggle, Gregory, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 39)
- Spilner, Candy, 1999-2005 (Box 52, Folder 40)
- Spinney, Alexandra, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 41)
- Spira, Bill, 1988-1999 (Box 52, Folder 42)
- Spiro, Yasmin, undated (Box 52, Folder 43)
- Spivak, Alexander Sasha, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 44)
- Spowart, Lesley, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 45)
- Spransy, Linnea, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 47)
- Spradling, Gary, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 46)
- Springer, Susan, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 48)
- Springfield, Molly, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 49)
- Srouji, Hanibal, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 50)
- St. Arnaud, Raymond, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 51)
- St. Germain, Michael, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- St. John, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- St-Jacques, Pierre, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 52)
- Staab, Roy, 1991-2000 (Box 52, Folder 53)
- Staerk, Ann Sophie, undated (Box 52, Folder 54)
- Stafford, Janet, 1996-2003 (Box 52, Folder 56)
- Stafford, Trevor, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 57)
- Stahl, Jolie, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 58)
- Stahl, Monika, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 59)
- Staiger, Alex, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 60)
- Stalder, Andrew, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 55)
- Stalder, Andrew, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 61)
- Staller, Jan, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 62)
- Stamos, William, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 63)
- Stamps, R.H., 2000 (Box 52, Folder 64)
- Stanbridge, Linda, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 65)
- Stanfield, Roy, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 66)
- Stanger, David, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 67)
- Stanojkovik, Saso, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 68)
- Stansbury, Jeremiah, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 69)
- Stanziola, Laura, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 70)
- Staples, Loretta, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 71)
- Starikov, Stan, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 72)
- Starkie, Jason, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 73)
- Starkweather, Andy, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 74)
- Starkweather, Jennifer, 1999-2004 (Box 52, Folder 75)
- Starr, Judy, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 76)
- Staschke, Dirk, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 77)
- Staub, Matt, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 48)
- Staub, Richard, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 78)
- Stavitsky, Ellen, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 79)
- Steadman, Ryan, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 80)
- Steckler, Debra, 1999-2003 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Stecko, Kathy, 1997-2005 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Steel, Gregory, 2002-2005 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Steele, Mary, 1987-2001 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Steen, Roger, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Steen, Sylvia, 1996-2000 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Steglitz, Ilene, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Stein, Anna, 2002-2005 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Stein, Isa, 1998-2000 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Stein, Jonathan, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Stein, Linda, 2004-2006 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Stein, Lynn, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Stein, Susan, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Steinberg, Julia, 1990-2000 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Steinmann, Margie, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Steinsnyder, Bonnie, 1999-2003 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Steinson, Nancy, 1991-2002 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Stella, Felis, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Stenger, Jeremy, 2001-2005 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Stepanian, Alysse, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Stephens, Richard, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Sterling, Colleen, 1989-1996 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Stern, Emily, 1999-2003 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Stern, Evie, 1985-1989 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Stern, Oona, 1996-2001 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Sterner, David, 1999-2002 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Stevens, Kerry, 2001-2004 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Stevenson, Sarah, 1990-1999 (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Stewart, Betsy, 1999-2000 (Box 53, Folder 28)
- Stewart, Dorothy, 1985-1996 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Stewart, Greg, 1993-1995 (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Stewart, Janet, 1987-1989 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Stiglich, Bruce, 1989-2001 (Box 64, Folder 73)
- Stiles, Judith N., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- Still, Sam, 2001-2005 (Box 53, Folder 33)
- St. Lewis, Louis, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 34)
- Stockbridge, Cath, 1999-2005 (Box 53, Folder 35)
- Stockdale-Wolfe, Ellen, 2003-2005 (Box 53, Folder 36)
- Stockton, Mark, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 37)
- Stoilov, Ivaylo, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 107)
- Stojakovic, Ivan, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 38)
- Stole, Andrew, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 39)
- Stoltzfus, Randall, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 40)
- Stolz, Claus, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 41)
- Stone, Cynthia, 1992-2001 (Box 53, Folder 42)
- Stone, Mark, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 43)
- Stone, Tamar, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 44)
- Storey, Amy, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 45)
- Strackbein, Ginna, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 46)
- Strausman, Albert, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 49)
- Steeves, Kari, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 72)
- Streicher, Robert, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 53)
- Stremple, Paul, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 50)
- Striga, Nicholas, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 51)
- Strnadova, Barbara, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 52)
- Strother, Margaret, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 71)
- Stroup, Derek, 1999-2003 (Box 53, Folder 54)
- Stuehmke, Edel, 1994-2001 (Box 53, Folder 55)
- Stuelke, Satre, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 56)
- Stumpf, Brenda, 2003-2005 (Box 53, Folder 57)
- Sturges, Ben, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 58)
- Sturhahn, Kelly, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 59)
- Stuttman, Paula, 1998-2000 (Box 53, Folder 60)
- Suarez, Daniel, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 61)
- Subramanian, Lila, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 62)
- Sudran, Deborah, 1997-2002 (Box 53, Folder 63)
- Sugar, Janos, 1995-1998 (Box 53, Folder 64)
- Sugden, Olga, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 65)
- Sugita, Toru, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 66)
- Sugitatsu, Yoshi, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 67)
- Suisman, Maggie, 1999-2003 (Box 53, Folder 68)
- Sullivan, Barbara, 1998-2000 (Box 53, Folder 69)
- Sullivan, Jennifer, 2000-2004 (Box 53, Folder 70)
- Sullivan, Patrice, 1988-2000 (Box 53, Folder 71)
- Sullivan, Shawn, 1999-2000 (Box 53, Folder 72)
- Sumerel, Holly, 1996-2000 (Box 53, Folder 73)
- Sun, Juju, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 75)
- Sun, Sara, 1996-2003 (Box 53, Folder 74)
- Sung, Eric, 2003-2005 (Box 53, Folder 76)
- Sung, Ming-Yi, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 70)
- Suran, William, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Susanj, Draga, 1999-2004 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Susplugas, Jeanne, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Sussman, Rachel, 1998-2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Suto, Ferenc, 1996-2004 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Sutphin, Katie, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Sutton, David, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Sutton, John Kevin, 1990-1999 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Sutton, Julia, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Suzuki, Takahiko, 1996-2003 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Svetvilas, Chanika, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Swack, Debra, 1988-2000 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Swan, Philip, 2003-2005 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Swanson, Charlee, 1994-2001 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Swanston, Thomas, 2002-2004 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Sweeney, Mary, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Sweeten, Natasha, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Sweibel, Liz, 2002-2005 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Swetcharnik, Sara, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Swetcharnik, William, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Swett, Benjamin, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Swift, Clive, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Swiszcz, Carolyn, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Syed, Farah, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Sylmor, Ruth, 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Szalla, Jason, 2002-2004 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Szczesny, Radek, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Sziladi, Monika, 1990-2003 (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Szilasi, Istvan, 1999-2001 (Box 64, Folder 74)
- Szot, Robert, 2001-2003 (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Szyper, Katrine, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Taber, Mark, 2003-2005 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Tafur, Catherine, 2001-2005 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Tahaney, Ed Celso, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Takagi, Koichiro, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Takai, Hanayo, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Takeuchi, Paul, 1996-1999 (Box 54, Folder 34)
- Talasco, Traci, 1997-2004 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Talbot, Nina, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 36)
- Taliano, Lisa, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Tall, Cheryl, 1997-2001 (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Talluto, Amy, 2001-2005 (Box 54, Folder 39)
- Tamayo, Amy, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 40)
- Tamsin, Tamara, 2001-2003 (Box 54, Folder 41)
- Tanner, Sarah, undated (Box 64, Folder 76)
- Tapiador, Millette, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 42)
- Tarentino, Leigh, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 43)
- Tassin, Sonia, 1998-2004 (Box 54, Folder 44)
- Tate, Jean, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Tatum, Grant, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 45)
- Taylor, Ann, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 46)
- Taylor, Gary, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 47)
- Taylor, Jean, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 48)
- Taylor, Joy, 1991-2001 (Box 54, Folder 49)
- Taylor, Katherine, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 50)
- Taylor, Kristine, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 51)
- Taylor, Philip, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 52)
- Taylor, Robin, 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 53)
- Taylor, Sunaura, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 54)
- Taylor, William Booth, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 55)
- Tcherkelov, Houben, 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 56)
- Tegeder, Dannielle, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 57)
- Teicher, Lois, 1992-2000 (Box 54, Folder 58)
- Teitelbaum, Ariel, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 59)
- Teixidor, Carmen, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 60)
- Telcocci, Gina, 2000-2005 (Box 54, Folder 61)
- Tempi and Wolf, 1989-1995 (Box 54, Folder 62)
- Temple, Kate, 1994-2003 (Box 54, Folder 63)
- Templeton, Eleanor, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 64)
- Teplin, Scott, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 65)
- Tepora, Jessica, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 66)
- Teraberry, Peter, 2001-2003 (Box 54, Folder 67)
- Terdoslavich, Daniel, undated (Box 54, Folder 69)
- Terpstra, Wesley, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 68)
- Terreson, Jeffrey, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 70)
- Terruso, Luigi, 1999-2003 (Box 54, Folder 71)
- Terry, Alexis, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 72)
- Tesauro, Giovanni, 1984-1994 (Box 54, Folder 74)
- Tesser, Julie, 1996-2003 (Box 54, Folder 73)
- Tessler, Roxanne, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- Thacher, Anita, 1981-1999 (Box 54, Folder 75)
- The Darkworld Project, 1999-2001 (Box 54, Folder 76)
- Theel, Gunnar, 1999-2001 (Box 54, Folder 77)
- Thiel, Haninga, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- Thijssens, Alex, 1989-2000 (Box 54, Folder 78)
- Thomas, Christopher, 1999-2000 (Box 54, Folder 79)
- Thomas, Dave, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 80)
- Thomas, Enrico, undated (Box 64, Folder 104)